Register of the Ronald I. McKinnon papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Ronald I. McKinnon papers
1952-2014
2015C20
Hoover Institution Archives
44 manuscript boxes (17.6 linear feet)
Correspondence and writings relating to international finance, especially to currency exchange.
McKinnon, Ronald I., 1935-2014.
Access
The collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2015.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
1935 July 10 Born, Edmonton, Canada
1956 Awarded B.A. degree, University of Alberta
1961 Awarded doctorate, University of Minnesota
1961 Joined the faculty of Stanford University as a professor of economics
1965 Author, The Implications of International Economic Integration for Monerary, Fiscal, and Exchange-Rate Policy
1973 Author, Money and Capital in Economic Development
1991 Author, The Order of Economic Liberalization: Financial Control in the Transition to a Market Economy
1996 Author, The Rules of the Game: International Money and Exchange Rates
2005 Author, Exchange Rates under the East Asian Dollar Standard: Living with Conflicted Virtue
2013 Author, The Unloved Dollar Standard: From Bretton Woods to the Rise of China
2014 Died
Scope and Content of Collection
Correspondence and writings relating to international finance, especially to currency exchange.
Economics.; Foreign exchange; International finance.
- Correspondence, 1981-2014
  - Aarstol, Mike, 1999 (Box-folder 1: 1)
  - Al-Demerdashi, Shireen, 2000 (Box-folder 1: 2)
  - Aliber, Robert, 2014 (Box-folder 1: 3)
  - Alphandéry, Edmond, 2011-2014 (Box-folder 1: 34)
  - Arndt, Sven, 2000 (Box-folder 1: 5)
  - Asmundson, Irena, 2002 (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Backes, Ben, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 1: 7)
  - Barczi, Nathan, 2001 (Box-folder 1: 8)
  - Barr, Alistair, 2002 (Box-folder 1: 9)
  - Barsky, Robert, 1997 (Box-folder 1: 10)
  - Bernstam, Michael, 2011 (Box-folder 1: 11)
  - Black, Stanley, 2006 (Box-folder 1: 12)
  - Bresnaham, Tim, 2002 (Box-folder 1: 13)
  - Brittan, Samuel, 1982-2000 (Box-folder 1: 14)
  - Broda, Christian, 2005 (Box-folder 1: 15)
  - Bulchandani, Ravi, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 1: 16)
  - Chang, Gene, 2004 (Box-folder 1: 17)
  - Charlier, Florence, 2000 (Box-folder 1: 18)
  - Chinoy, Sajjid, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 1: 19)
  - Choi, E. Kwan, 2004 (Box-folder 1: 20)
  - Choi, Winnie, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 1: 21)
  - Coates, Ken, 2002 (Box-folder 1: 22)
  - Connolly, Michael, 2007 (Box-folder 1: 23)
  - Corbo, Vittorio, 1986 (Box-folder 1: 24)
  - Corden, W. Max, 1993-2010 (Box-folder 1: 25)
  - Couharde, Cécile, 2007 (Box-folder 1: 26)
  - Del Buono, Michel, 2010 (Box-folder 1: 27)
  - Dozen, Toshinori, 2000 (Box-folder 2: 1)
  - Drysdale, Peter, 2014 (Box-folder 2: 2)
  - Eberle, William D., 1997 (Box-folder 2: 3)
  - Fang, Xinghai, 2005 (Box-folder 2: 4)
  - Feng, Xiaoming, 2013 (Box-folder 2: 5)
  - Ferguson, Niall, 2003 (Box-folder 2: 6)
  - Financial Times (Box-folder 2: 7)
  - Fratianni, Michele, 2011 (Box-folder 2: 8)
  - Friedman, Milton, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 2: 9)
  - Fung, K. C., 2003 (Box-folder 2: 10)
  - Glick, Reuven, 1997-2003 (Box-folder 2: 11)
  - Goulder, Larry, 2001 (Box-folder 2: 12)
  - Gray, Colin T., 2011 (Box-folder 2: 13)
  - Greenspan, Alan, 1998 (Box-folder 2: 14)
  - Guofeng, Sun (Box-folder 2: 15)
  - Gyohten, Toyoo, 1998 (Box-folder 2: 16)
  - Hanke, Steve, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 2: 17)
  - Hanssens, Dominique, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 2: 18)
  - Heng, Michael, 2013 (Box-folder 2: 19)
  - Hicks, John, 1987 (Box-folder 2: 20)
  - Hussman, John P., 1992 (Box-folder 2: 21)
  - I nternational Economy, 2009-2014 (Box-folder 2: 22)
  - Ito, Takatoshi, 2000 (Box-folder 2: 23)
  - Jackson, Lee, 2011 (Box-folder 3: 1)
  - Journal of African Economics, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 3: 2)
  - Journal of Economic Education, 2003 (Box-folder 3: 3)
  - Kannan, Prakesh, 2007 (Box-folder 3: 4)
  - Kirchline, James L., 1982 (Box-folder 3: 5)
  - Kohsaka, Akira, 1987 (Box-folder 3: 6)
  - Lacayo, Raúl, 1991 (Box-folder 3: 7)
  - Le, Nhat, 2000 (Box-folder 3: 8)
  - Levich, Richard, 2007 (Box-folder 3: 9)
  - Li, Jing, 2014 (Box-folder 3: 10)
  - Li, Nan, 2010-2014 (Box-folder 3: 11)
  - Liu, Zhao, 2011 (Box-folder 3: 12)
  - Lombardi, Domenico, 2005 (Box-folder 3: 13)
  - MacDonald, Ronald, 1994 (Box-folder 3: 14)
  - Makin, John, 2000 (Box-folder 3: 15)
  - Meng, Cai, 2014 (Box-folder 3: 16)
  - MIT Press
    - 1995-2002 (Box-folder 3: 17)
    - 2004-2014 (Box-folder 3: 18)
  - Nadeem, Sanaa, 2011 (Box-folder 3: 19)
  - Naknoi, Kanda, 2001 (Box-folder 3: 20)
  - New York Times, 2000 (Box-folder 3: 21)
  - Ng, Anita, 1994 (Box-folder 3: 22)
  - NIcholson, David, 2007 (Box-folder 3: 23)
  - Ohno, Kenichi, 1999-2005 (Box-folder 3: 24)
  - Ortiz, Guillermo, 1997-2012 (Box-folder 4: 1)
  - Oxford University Press, 2012-2014 (Box-folder 4: 2)
  - Ozler, Sule, 2000 (Box-folder 4: 3)
  - Parapiboom, Potay, 2008 (Box-folder 4: 4)
  - Pencavel, John, 2010 (Box-folder 4: 5)
  - Pill, Huw, 1995-2011 (Box-folder 4: 6)
  - Porter, Michael, 1998 (Box-folder 4: 7)
  - Preeg, Ernest, 2014 (Box-folder 4: 8)
  - Princeton University Press, 2006 (Box-folder 4: 9)
  - Pringle, Robert, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 4: 10)
  - Qian, Yingyi, 2014 (Box-folder 4: 11)
  - Qiao, Helen, 2011-2014 (Box-folder 4: 12)
  - Ramstetter, Eric O., 2012 (Box-folder 4: 13)
  - Reinhart, Carmen M., 2010 (Box-folder 4: 14)
  - Roberts, Molly, 2008 (Box-folder 4: 15)
  - Rosston, Greg, 2012 (Box-folder 4: 16)
  - Routledge, 2009 (Box-folder 4: 17)
  - Rozelle, Scott, 2009 (Box-folder 4: 18)
  - Salvatore, Dominick, 2012 (Box-folder 4: 19)
  - Shultz, George, 2010 (Box-folder 4: 20)
  - Smick, David, 1998 (Box-folder 4: 21)
  - Sprinkel, Beryl W., 1982 (Box-folder 4: 22)
  - Stanford University Overseas Studies Program, 2002 (Box-folder 4: 23)
  - Stein, Benn, 2010-2013 (Box-folder 5: 1)
  - Summers, Lawrence R., 1997-1999 (Box-folder 5: 2)
  - Swallow, Adam, 2013 (Box-folder 5: 3)
  - Taylor, John, 2001-2014 (Box-folder 5: 4)
  - Thygesen, NIels Christoffer, 2014 (Box-folder 5: 5)
  - Tilton, Andrew, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 5: 6)
  - Tosborvorn, Art, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 5: 7)
  - Uzan, Marc (Box-folder 5: 8)
  - Volcker, Paul, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 5: 9)
  - Wall Steet Journal, 2009-2013 (Box-folder 5: 10)
  - Wallich, Henry C., 1982 (Box-folder 5: 11)
  - Wang, David, 2013 (Box-folder 5: 12)
  - Wang, Di, 2013 (Box-folder 5: 13)
  - Warsop, Neil, 2002 (Box-folder 5: 14)
  - Wolf, Martin, 2001-2011 (Box-folder 5: 15)
  - World Bank, 2001-2010 (Box-folder 5: 16)
  - World Economy
    - 2004 (Box-folder 5: 17)
    - 2011 (Box-folder 5: 18)
  - Wright, Mark L., 2002 (Box-folder 5: 19)
  - Wyplosz, Charles, 2007 (Box-folder 5: 20)
  - Ye, Lei, 2007 (Box-folder 5: 21)
  - Yeh, Annie, 2012 (Box-folder 5: 22)
  - Yoshida, Naoto, 2001 (Box-folder 5: 23)
  - Young, Warren, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 5: 24)
  - Yu, Ding, 2013 (Box-folder 5: 25)
  - Zettelmeyer, Jeronimo, 2001 (Box-folder 5: 26)
  - Zhang, Sujiang, 2010 (Box-folder 5: 27)
- Speeches and Writings, 1982-2014
  - Reviews of books by McKinnon, 1991-2006 (Box-folder 6: 1)
  - "British Monetary Policy, Exchange Rates, and International Monetary Reform, 1982 (Box-folder 6: 2)
  - "Comment on Helliwell's Comparative Macroeconomics", 1988 January 15 (Box-folder 6: 3)
  - "Alternative International Monetary Systems: A Historical Perspective, 1989 (Box-folder 6: 4)
  - "The International Gold Standard: 1879-1913", 1989 May (Box-folder 6: 5)
  - "The Exchange Rate and the Trade Balance: Insular versus Open Economies", 1990 (Box-folder 6: 6)
  - "Spontaneous Order on the Road Back from Socialism: An Asian perspective", 1992 January 3-5 (Box-folder 6: 7)
  - "Financial Control in China's Transition to a Market Economy", 1992 December 16 (Box-folder 6: 8)
  - "World Development and Economic Institutions", 1993 January 4 (Box-folder 6: 9)
  - "The Rules of the Game: International Money in Historical Perspective", 1993 March (Box-folder 6: 10)
  - "Market-Preserving Fiscal Federalism: Notes on the American and Chinese Models", 1993 August 1 (Box-folder 6: 11)
  - "Financial Growth and Marcoeconomic Stability in China, 1978-92: Implications for Russia and Other Transitional Economcies", 1993 September (Box-folder 6: 12)
  - "The Syndrome of the Ever-Higher Yen", 1993 September 27 (Box-folder 6: 13)
  - "China: Financial Dimensions of Economic Development", 1994 January 7 (Box-folder 6: 14)
  - "Economic Reform in China: A Political Perspective", 1994 January 27 (Box-folder 6: 15)
  - "Dollar and Yen: The Problem of Financial Adjustment between the United States and Japan", 1994 August (Box-folder 6: 16)
  - "Market-Preserving Fiscal Federalism: The Conditions of Money and Credit", 1994 November 23-24 (Box-folder 6: 17)
  - "Intergovernmental Competition in Europe with and without a Common Currency", 1995 March 2 (Box-folder 6: 18)
  - Gradual versus Rapid Industrialization in Socialist Economies: Financial Policies in China and Russia Compared, 1994 (Box-folder 6: 19)
  - "A Common Monetary Standard or a Common Currency for Europe?", 1994 November (Box-folder 6: 20)
  - "Mexico's Financial Crisis: Overborrowing or Overlending?", 1995 January 11 (Box-folder 6: 21)
  - "Intergovernmental Competition in Europe with and without a Common Currency", 1995 March 2 (Box-folder 6: 22)
  - "Lessons on Sequencing Financial Reforms in Agriculture: A Perspective on Egypt, 1995 August 4 (Box-folder 6: 23)
  - "The Plaza Agreement 10 Years Later", 1995 September 8 (Box-folder 6: 24)
  - "Exchange Rates and Inflation: China, Hong Kong, and the United States, 1996 June (Box-folder 6: 25)
  - "Interpreting Exchange Rates and Inflation in China and Hong Kong Compared to the United States and Japan", 1996 August (Box-folder 6: 26)
  - Review of Financial Reform in China, 1996 August 26 (Box-folder 6: 27)
  - With Huw Pill, "Credible Economic Liberalizations and Over-Borrowing", 1997 January 18 (Box-folder 6: 28)
  - "The Euro versus the Dollar as International Money", 1998 April (Box-folder 6: 29)
  - "The Birth of the Euro", 1999 September 3 (Box-folder 6: 30)
  - "The American Boom and International Credit", 2000 January 22 (Box-folder 6: 31)
  - "Mundell, the Euro, and Optimum Currency Areas", 2000 May 22 (Box-folder 6: 32)
  - "Evaluating the Euro's Performance", 2000 May 23 (Box-folder 6: 33)
  - "China's Financial Policies upon Accession to the WTO", 2000 July 17 (Box-folder 6: 34)
  - "Is Macroeconomics Dead?", 2000 July 18 (Box-folder 6: 35)
  - "On the Periphery of the International Dollar Standard: Canada versus Latin America versus East Asia", 2000 August 28 (Box-folder 7: 1)
  - "Can the World Economy Afford American Tax Cuts?: The International Dollar Standard Redux", 2001 February 6 (Box-folder 7: 2)
  - "Japan's Banking Crisis and Low Interest-Rate Trap", 2001 May 1 (Box-folder 7: 3)
  - "Restoring Argentina's Financial Health", 2001 August 27 (Box-folder 7: 4)
  - "The World Dollar Standard and the East Asian Rate Dilemma", 2001 December 11 (Box-folder 7: 5)
  - "The East Asian Exchange Rate Dilemma and the World Dollar Standard", 2002 February 26 (Box-folder 7: 6)
  - Review of Tirole, Jean, Financial Crises, Liquidity, and the International Monetary System, 2002 (Box-folder 7: 7)
  - With Rishi Goyal, "Japan's Negative Risk Premium in Interest Rates: The Liquidity Trap and Fall in Bank Lending", 2002 March (Box-folder 7: 8)
  - With Gunther Schnabl, "Synchronized Business Cycle in East Asia and Fluctuations in the Yen/Dollar Exchange Rate", 2003 January (Box-folder 7: 9)
  - "Why Is It a Good Thing for Japan's Economy to Fix the Exchange Rate at 1 Dollar=120 Yen?", 2003 June 19 (Box-folder 7: 10)
  - Review of Helliwell, John F., Globalization and Well-Being, 2003 July 3 (Box-folder 7: 11)
  - "The World Dollar Standard and Globalization: New Rules for the Game?", 2003 August (Box-folder 7: 12)
  - With Gunther Schnabl, "Synchronised Business Cycles in East Asia", 2003 August (Box-folder 7: 13)
  - "Optimum Currency Areas and Key Currencies: Mundell I versus Mundell II", 2003 November (Box-folder 7: 14)
  - "Government Deficits and the Deindustrialization of America", 2004 (Box-folder 7: 15)
  - "The East Asian Dollar Standard", 2004 April 16 (Box-folder 7: 16)
  - With Gunther Schnabl, "The Return to Soft Dollar Pegging in East Asia: Mitigating Conflicted Virtue", 2004 July (Box-folder 7: 17)
  - "China's Dysfunctional Currency Basket", 2005 October 2 (Box-folder 7: 18)
  - "U.S. Fiscal Deficits and Lost Jobs in Manufacturing", 2004 November 5 (Box-folder 7: 19)
  - "China's New Exchange Rate Policy: Will China Follow Japan into a Liquidity Trap?", 2005 October 8 (Box-folder 7: 20)
  - "China's Exchange Rate Appreciation in the Light of the Earlier Japanese Experience", 2006 (Box-folder 7: 21)
  - With Gunther Schnabl, "Devaluing the Dollar: A Critical Analysis of William Cline's Case for a New Plaza Agreement", 2006 April (Box-folder 7: 22)
  - Preface and afterward to second edition of Money and Capital in Economic Development, 2006 March (Box-folder 7: 23)
  - With Gunther Schnabl, "China's Exchange Rate and International Adjustment in Wages, Prices, and Interest Rates: Japan Déjà Vu?", 2006 April 20 (Box-folder 7: 24)
  - Testimony before Congressional committee on China's financial system and monetary policies, 2006 August 22 (Box-folder 7: 25)
  - Encyclopedia entry on conflicted virtue, 2006 September 9 (Box-folder 7: 26)
  - Encyclopedia entry on the dollar standard, 2006 September 10 (Box-folder 7: 27)
  - "Mckinnon on the Dollar in a Nutshell", 2006 December 27 (Box-folder 7: 28)
  - "Japan's Deflationary Hangover: Wage Stagnation and the Syndrome of the Ever-Weaker Yen", 2007 July (Box-folder 8: 1)
  - Review of Eichengreen, Barry, Global Imbalances and t he Lessons of Bretton Woods, 2007 July 3 (Box-folder 8: 2)
  - "The Exchange Rate as a Monetary Anchor Post-Crisis: Argentina versus Korea", 2007 September (Box-folder 8: 3)
  - "Conflicted Virtue", 2007 November (Box-folder 8: 4)
  - "Dollar Standard", 2007 November (Box-folder 8: 5)
  - "U.S. Current Account Deficits and the Dollar Standard's Sustainability: A Monetary Approach", 2007 December (Box-folder 8: 6)
  - "China and the United States: Partners for Managing the Global Economic Crisis?", 2008 August 27 (Box-folder 8: 7)
  - "Unblocking Credit Markets by Reducing Counterparty Risk", 2008 October 2008 (Box-folder 8: 8)
  - With Gunther Schnabl, "China's Financial Conundrum and Global Imbalances", 2009 March (Box-folder 8: 9)
  - With Gunther Schnabl, "China's Global Imbalances and the Fiscal, Monetary and Exchange Rate Response to the Global Financial Crisis, 2009 June (Box-folder 8: 10)
  - With Brian Lee nad Yi David Wang, "The Global Credit Crisis and China's Exchange Rate", 2009 October (Box-folder 8: 11)
  - "U.S. Exit Strategies and Zero Interest Rates", 2009 (Box-folder 8: 12)
  - With Brian Lee and Yi David Wang, "The Global Credit Crisis and China's Exchange Rate", 2010 (Box-folder 8: 13)
  - "A Stable Yuan/Dollar Rate Forever?", 2010 March 11 (Box-folder 8: 14)
  - Letter to the editor of The Economist, 2010 August 21 (Box-folder 8: 15)
  - "Why China Shouldn't Float", 2010 Fall (Box-folder 8: 16)
  - "Beggar-Thy-Neighbor Interest Rate Policies", 2010 November (Box-folder 8: 17)
  - "A New Exchange Rate or New Interest Regime?: A Post Mortem on the G-20 in Seoul", 2010 November 17 (Box-folder 8: 18)
  - "Carry Trades, Interest Differentials, and International Monetary Reform", 2011 (Box-folder 8: 19)
  - With Gunther Schnabl, "China and Its Dollar Exchange Rate: A Worldwide Stabilising Influence?", 2011 (Box-folder 8: 20)
  - "The Unloved Dollar Standard", 2011 (Box-folder 8: 21)
  - "The Fed on the Cusp of Worldwide Inflation", 2011 February 3 (Box-folder 8: 22)
  - With Gunther Schnabl, "China and Its Exchange Rate: A Worldwide Stabilizing Influence?", 2011 May (Box-folder 8: 23)
  - "Alexander Hamilton on Sovereign Debt Crises, 2011 September (Box-folder 8: 24)
  - "The Conservative Case for a Wealth Tax", 2012 January 16 (Box-folder 8: 25)
  - "Zero Interest Rates Provoke World Monetary Instability and Constrict the U.S. Economy", 2012 July 30 (Box-folder 8: 26)
  - With Zhao Liu, "Hot Money Flows, Commodity Price Cycles, and Financial Repression in the US and the People's Republic of China" The (Box-folder 8: 27)
  - "The U.S. Saving Deficiency, Current-Account Deficits, and Deindustrialization: Implications for China", 2013 February 6 (Box-folder 8: 28)
  - With Zhao Lilu, "Modern Currency Wars: The United States versus Japan", 2013 June 19 (Box-folder 8: 29)
  - "Tapering without Tears", 2013 September 28 (Box-folder 8: 30)
  - With Zhao Liu, "Financial Disintermediation in the US and Its Impact on Business Lending", 2014 January 21 (Box-folder 8: 31)
  - With Gunther Schnabl, "China's Exchange Rate and Financial Repression: The Conflicted Emergence of the Renmibi as an International Currency, 2014 February (Box-folder 8: 32)
  - "China's Currency Conundrum", 2014 April 25 (Box-folder 8: 33)
  - "Breton [Bretton] Woods Reconsidered: The Dollar Standard and the Role of China", 2014 August (Box-folder 8: 34)
- Conference Materials, 1993-2014
  - Vatican seminar, 1993 January 4 (Box-folder 9: 1)
  - American Economic Association and Chinese Economist Society conference, 1995 January 6-8 (Box-folder 9: 2)
  - "Historical Credibility: Implications for the Reform of the International Monetary System" conference, 1999 May 15 (Box-folder 9: 3)
  - Queen's University conference in honor of Robert Mundell, 2000 May (Box-folder 9: 4)
  - "International Economic Issues: Managing Monetary Policy in a Weakening Global Environment" conference, 2001 January 19 (Box-folder 9: 5)
  - "Monetary Outlook on East Asia in an Integrating World Economy" conference, 2001 September 5-6 (Box-folder 9: 6)
  - European Bank for Reconstruction and Development 10th anniversary conference, 2001 December 13-14 (Box-folder 9: 7)
  - "Japan's Lost Decade: Origins, Consequences and Prospects for Recovery" symposium, 2002 March 22 (Box-folder 9: 8)
  - "The Korean Economy Beyond the Crisis" conference, 2002 October 4-5 (Box-folder 9: 9)
  - Issues in International Policy seminar, 2004 October 5 (Box-folder 9: 10)
  - "Macroeconomic Stability, Financial Markets amd Economic Development" conference, 2002 November 12-13 (Box-folder 9: 11)
  - Seventh International Advisory Council Meeting of the China Development Bank, 2005 October 25-28 (Box-folder 10: 1)
  - Merrill Lynch Japan Conference, 2006 September 6-8 (Box-folder 10: 2)
  - "Public Policies under Globalization" conference, 2007 February 27 (Box-folder 10: 3)
  - "Monetary Policy under Uncertainty", 2007 June 4-5 (Box-folder 10: 4)
  - "Sustaining China's Growth", 2007 September 16-18 (Box-folder 10: 5)
  - "Whither Monetary Policy?" conference, 2008 June 26-27 (Box-folder 10: 6)
  - European Central Bank conference, 2008 October 13 (Box-folder 10: 7)
  - "Global Financial Crisis: The Way forward" conference, 2010 April 9 (Box-folder 10: 8)
  - Santa Cruz Institute for International Economics conference, 2009 October 2-3 (Box-folder 10: 9)
  - "India's Economic Reforms: Emerging Challenges for the Country and the New Government" conference, 2009 October 21-23 (Box-folder 10: 10)
  - Conference in honor of Paul De Grauwe, 2011 November 17-18 (Box-folder 11: 1)
  - "Asia's Role in the Post-Crisis Global Economy" conference, 2011 November 28-30 (Box-folder 11: 2)
  - Singapore Economic Review Conference, 2011 August 4-6 (Box-folder 11: 3)
  - Singapore Economic Review Conference, 2011 August 4-6 (Box-folder 11: 3)
  - "Poly U 75th Anniversary Conference: Stabilizing the World Economy", 2012 November 14 (Box-folder 11: 4)
  - "2012 Caixin Summit: China and the World" conference, 2012 November 16-17 (Box-folder 11: 5)
  - International Monetary Fund seminar, 2013 March 5-7 (Box-folder 11: 6)
  - Asian Development Bank Institute seminar, 2012 May 2-7 (Box-folder 11: 7)
  - "Currency Arrangements and the Global Monetary Crisis" conference, 2013 July 5-7 (Box-folder 11: 8)
  - "Prospects for Asia and the Global Economy" conference, 2013 November 3-5 (Box-folder 11: 9)
  - "The Federal Reserve's Role in the Global Economy: A Historical Perspective" conference, 2014 April 3-4 (Box-folder 11: 10)
  - "Economic Priorities for the New Government" conference, 2014 June 2-3 (Box-folder 11: 11)
  - "Bretton Woods: The Founders and the Future" conference, 2014 September 2-5 (Box-folder 11: 12)
  - "The European Banking Union and Its Future" conference, 2014 September 14-15 (Box-folder 11: 13)
- Writings by Others, 1952-2012
  - Abramovitz, Moses, 1989 March (Box-folder 12: 1)
  - Aghion, Philippe, 1996 April 4 (Box-folder 12: 2)
  - Agrawal, Pradeep, 1999 July (Box-folder 12: 3)
  - Ajayi, Kehinde, 2004 March (Box-folder 12: 4)
  - Akerlof, George A., 1996 (Box-folder 12: 5)
  - Allen, Franklin, 2000 July 12 (Box-folder 12: 6)
  - Alogoskoufis, George S., 1989-1992 (Box-folder 12: 7)
  - Anderson, Jonathan, 2005 January 25 (Box-folder 12: 8)
  - Arrow, Kenneth J.
    - 1952-1965 (Box-folder 12: 9)
    - 1969-1972 (Box-folder 12: 10)
  - Arslanalp, Serkan, 2004 (Box-folder 12: 11)
  - Arteta, Carlos Óscar, 2001 November 4 (Box-folder 12: 12)
  - Artis, Michael J., 1985-1997 (Box-folder 12: 13)
  - Aturpane, Chonira, 2000 May 9 (Box-folder 13: 1)
  - Bahl, Roy, 1992 February (Box-folder 13: 2)
  - Banerjee, Abhijit, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 13: 3)
  - Barajas, Adolfo, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 13: 4)
  - Bayoumi, Tamim, 1989-1997 (Box-folder 13: 5)
  - Bednar, Jenna, 1995 (Box-folder 13: 6)
  - Berger, Frederick E., 1979 (Box-folder 13: 7)
  - Bergin, Paul R., 1995 (Box-folder 13: 8)
  - Bergsten, Fred, 2000 July 15 (Box-folder 13: 9)
  - Bernanke, Ben S., 1995 (Box-folder 13: 10)
  - Bernard, Andrew B., 2002 August 16 (Box-folder 13: 11)
  - Bernholz, Peter, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 13: 12)
  - Bernstam, Michael, 1993 (Box-folder 13: 13)
  - Bhagwati, Jagdish, 1967-2005 (Box-folder 14: 1)
  - Bird, Richard M., 2002 (Box-folder 14: 2)
  - Bisignano, Joseph, 2003 January (Box-folder 14: 3)
  - Bloomfield, Arthur I., 1959 (Box-folder 14: 4)
  - Bomfim, Antúlo, 1994 (Box-folder 14: 5)
  - Bardo, Michael D.
    - 1989-1995 (Box-folder 14: 6)
    - 1998 (Box-folder 14: 7)
    - 2005 (Box-folder 14: 8)
    - 2011 (Box-folder 14: 9)
  - Bottelier, Pieter, 2003 (Box-folder 14: 10)
  - Brada, Joseph C., 2001 (Box-folder 14: 11)
  - Broadway, Robin W., 1994 November (Box-folder 14: 12)
  - Brock, Philip, 1982-1996 (Box-folder 15: 1)
  - Broda, Christian, 2007 July (Box-folder 15: 2)
  - Buiter, Willem H., 2001-2007 (Box-folder 15: 3)
  - Burkett, Paul, 1985-1992 (Box-folder 15: 4)
  - Calomiris, George W., 1998 (Box-folder 15: 5)
  - Calvo, Guillermo, 2002 May (Box-folder 15: 6)
  - Cesarano, Filippo, 2005 (Box-folder 15: 7)
  - Chai, Jingqing, 1998 August (Box-folder 15: 8)
  - Chairoj, Soravit, 2003 (Box-folder 16: 1)
  - Charlier, Florence
    - 1999 (Box-folder 16: 2)
    - 2000-2002 (Box-folder 16: 3)
  - Chinoy, Saijid, 2001 (Box-folder 16: 4)
  - Choi, Winnie, 2002 August (Box-folder 16: 5)